<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>it on Random forest</title>
    <link>http://sarg.org.ru/tags/it/</link>
    <description>Recent content in it on Random forest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://sarg.org.ru/tags/it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>📖 Cracking The Code To A Successful Interview</title>
      <link>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/cracking-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/cracking-interview/</guid>
      <description>Goodreads - 3/5.
First impression: Overall the tone of the book is slightly arrogant. The author&amp;rsquo;s ego is soaking from every page.
After the read: The book is best suited for a sales position in corporate America. Overall the message of the book is: Be prepared, know what&amp;rsquo;s expected of you and give it to the inverviewer in advance. In chapter 9 there is a summary of REAPRICH method. Chapter 10-12,15 are unrelated to hiring process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>📖 Growing Object-Oriented Softwared, Guided by Tests.</title>
      <link>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/tdd-freeman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/tdd-freeman/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finished reading Growing Object-Oriented Softwared, Guided by Tests by Steve Freeman and Nat Pryce. The book is a good introduction into TDD. First it goes through core concepts and then demonstrates how to implement TDD on a simple project.
My takeouts throughout the reading:
 TDD is a core practice of XP. TDD is not about keeping defects from the users, but helping the team to understand the features and to deliver them reliably and predictably.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting watch list from TMDb</title>
      <link>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/tmdb-export/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/tmdb-export/</guid>
      <description>I keep list of movies I&amp;rsquo;ve watched on TheMovieDB. The service is great and I&amp;rsquo;ve used it for quite a long time (&amp;gt;700 movies in my list). I was using another service before, which unfortunately had closed without giving me a chance to export the data and I had to scrape my watchlist from google cache.
To prevent that from happening again, I&amp;rsquo;ve exported my watchlist from TMDb and will use the service only as a secondary source with nice UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android apps that I use</title>
      <link>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/android-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/android-apps/</guid>
      <description>My phone is running AOSP without google services and almost all of the applications I use come from F-Droid. Few exceptions are apps for paid services that I use and they are installed from Aurora Store.
 I use fdroidcl to install and update applications. Backup is covered in post &amp;ldquo;Backing up Android phone&amp;rdquo;. I use syncthing to share a directory between my laptops and phone. I have &amp;ldquo;Password Store&amp;rdquo; files in the shared directory in case I need access to passwords on phone (rarely).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backing up Android phone</title>
      <link>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/android-backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/android-backup/</guid>
      <description>One day my wife asked me to help her backup about 30Gb of photos from her android phone. At first we had tried to copy files over MTP (in Win10). This idea quickly showed its incapacity. You see, Win10 wants to be nice and tries to calculate ETA. But 30Gb is a lot of files and over MTP it takes one request per file to get its size. So, we waited half an hour while Win10 was preparing to start the transfer and I had aborted this madness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making hugo powered blog in emacs</title>
      <link>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/emacs-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/emacs-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Starting a blog this days couldn&amp;rsquo;t be easier. Ten simple steps to get started.&amp;lt;!&amp;ndash;more&amp;ndash;&amp;gt;
  Create a repo for github pages.
Every file you put in the repo would be published automatically:
By default, Jekyll doesn&amp;#39;t build files or folders that: are located in a folder called /node_modules or /vendor start with _, ., or # end with are excluded by the exclude setting in your configuration file   Configure custom domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exporting secrets from FreeOTP to Pass</title>
      <link>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/freeotp-to-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/freeotp-to-pass/</guid>
      <description>I have broken my phone screen. Not a big deal but I use it for 2FA. While replacement is on the way I will extract credentials from FreeOTP and import them in password store. Be aware that it is completeley against the idea of 2FA, because now both password and otp are on the same device. &amp;lt;!&amp;ndash;more&amp;ndash;&amp;gt;
So, first I need to find where FreeOTP stores OTP secrets. Android apps usually use sqlite db for that, but not in this case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get the brain off the instant gratification hook</title>
      <link>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/telega-otp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarg.org.ru/blog/telega-otp/</guid>
      <description>It easily becomes automatic to check for notifications/new messages/new emails etc. To give my rational self some time to intercept compulsive behaviour I have made this elisp snippet.
&amp;lt;!&amp;ndash;more&amp;ndash;&amp;gt;
(defun sarg/otp-for-confirm () &amp;#34;Generates random hex string&amp;#34; (format &amp;#34;%06x%06x%06x&amp;#34; (random (expt 16 6)) (random (expt 16 6)) (random (expt 16 6)))) (defun confirm-advice (proc &amp;amp;rest args) &amp;#34;Asks to enter random string as confirmation before executing PROC.&amp;#34; (interactive) (let* ((pass (sarg/otp-for-confirm)) (input (read-string (format &amp;#34;Enter %s if you wish to proceed: &amp;#34; pass)))) (if (string= input pass) (apply proc args)))) ;; Apply the advice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
